>> Jem: 你今天学到了很多。
&gt;&gt; Jem: You have learned so much today.
说实话我为你们的网站工作感到骄傲
And honestly, I'm proud of you all for
getting your website working.
如果没有其他的，你的网站就在运行，它在 HV2上运行，
If nothing else, you have your
website running, it's running on HV2,
在最新的事情上跑来了
running on the latest things.
您希望它现在有一个 Web 套接字连接，因此
You hopefully it now have
a web socket connection so
你可以用网络套接字来做一些很有力的事情
you can do some really powerful
things with web sockets.
但你已经完成了整个旅程
But you've completed the journey,
you've completed full stack.
我现在可以说你是个完全的工程师吗
I can say at this point,
are you a full stack engineer?
对我来说够近的了
Close enough for me.
>> 演讲者 2: [LAUGH] >> Jem: Nice 作业，每个人。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Jem: Nice job, everyone.
我想这会把它包起来的
And I think that'll wrap it up.
除非有人有最后的问题
Unless anybody has any final questions,
thoughts,
你想和我分享的智慧的珍珠
pearls of wisdom you'd
like to share with me.
你说的事杰姆错了
Things you said, Jem is wrong.
我只是不想在课堂上说
And I just didn't want to say it in class.
但现在我们可以说了
But now we can say it.
>> Jem: 好酷。
&gt;&gt; Jem: All right cool.
好的谢谢你听我说
All right, thanks for listening.
>> 扬声器 2: [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [APPLAUSE]